I. M. Pei Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Oversize, 1958-2009 (Box OV 1-OV 49)
  - Miscellany
    - Awards and honors
      - Award certificate, National Institute of Arts and Letters, 1961 (Container 480, Arnold Brunner Award) (Box OV 16)
      - Certificate of appointment, National Council of the Humanities, signed by Lyndon B. Johnson, 1966 (Container 480, Membership) (Box OV 27)
      - Citation from the Citizens Union of the City of New York, 1967 (Container 480, 1967, Albert S. Bard) (Box OV 13)
      - Award certificate from the City Club of New York, 1973 (Container 480, 1973, "For New York" Award) (Box OV 13)
      - Membership certificate, Royal Institute of British Architects, 1975 (Container 480, 1975, Membership) (Box OV 13)
      - Citation for distinguished achievement for the East Building of the National Gallery of Art, American Institute of Architects, 1978 (Container 480, 1978-1979, Gold Medal) (Box OV 13)
      - Certificate for the Gold Medal award, American Institute of Architects, 1979 (Container 480, 1978-1979, Gold Medal) (Box OV 43)
      - Certificate from the American Philosophical Society, 1981 (Container 481, 1980s, Miscellaneous) (Box OV 27)
      - Certificates from the Hong Kong Institute of Architects and the Board of Supervisors, Santa Clara County, Calif., 1985-1986 (Container 481, 1980s, Miscellaneous) (Box OV 13)
      - Certificate, New York City Mayor's Award of Honor for Arts and Culture, 1981 (Container 481, Mayor's Award) (Box OV 27)
      - Certificate, Personnalité de 1'année, Beaux Arts Committee, 1985 (Container 482, Personnalité) (Box OV 27)
      - Award certificate, American Institute of Architects, 1991 (Container 483, R. S. Reynolds Memorial Award) (Box OV 27)
      - Certificate proclaiming "I. M. Pei Day" by the mayor of New York City and citation from the president of the Borough of Manhattan, 1993 (Container 484, "I. M. Pei Day") (Box OV 13)
      - Award certificate from the Friends of Bezalel Academy of Arts and Design, 1994 (Container 484, Jerusalem Prize) (Box OV 27)
      - Award certificate from the New York State Association of Architects, 1995 (Container 484, Fellows Award) (Box OV 16)
      - Honorary membership certificate, Hong Kong chapter of the American Institute of Architects, 1999 (Container 485, Honorary Membership) (Box OV 13)
    - Education
      - Diploma, master's degree in architecture, Harvard University, 1946 (Container 488, Harvard University) (Box OV 13)
    - Exhibitions
      - Poster from exhibition "Drawings for the East Building, National Gallery of Art," Union Gallery, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, Mich., 1980 (Container 488, 1980, general) (Box OV 27)
      - Poster from "A Tribute to I.M. Pei" exhibition, Gregg Galleries, New York, N.Y., 1981 (Container 489, Gregg Galleries) (Box OV 13)
      - Poster from the "Paris: Grands Projets" exhibition, United States Custom House, New York, N.Y., 1988 (Container 489, 1988, Paris) (Box OV 44)
    - Honorary degree, University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong, 1990 (Container 491, University of Hong Kong) (Box OV 27)